You really can see the stars tonight.
Did you know that every star has a name?
That bright one is Sirius.
Those three lined up are Orion's Belt.
Brr!
Aren't you cold?
Come snuggle up.
And over there--that little cluster
of stars is Pleiades.
Oh, and that one--
Girls! Dinner's almost ready!
--Coming!
Shido... Shido? Shido, do you copy?
Kotori? Yeah, I'm good.
Mukuro's happiness is rising.
If this keeps up, it'll soon be
high enough to seal her powers.
Shido, we've got your back,
so just proceed with the date.
--Got it.
--What have you been mumbling about?
Eh? S-Sorry!
Say...
...what did you have in mind
that would make Muku happy?
Um... Well, there're lots of things.
Then show me all of them.
Let's get going.
Uh... H-Hold up!
Your hair's getting dirty.
We've gotta do something about how
long it is. Why not cut it and--?
Nay!
I refuse to have it cut,
even if it's you asking.
Sorry. I can't remember why,
but I'm against it.
I-I see. Sorry to ask that.
Still, we can't leave it like that.
Are you against tying it up?
No, just cutting it.
What should we do?
Um... Let's see...
We're getting some choices.
"1. Let a pro do her hair."
"2. Have Shido tie it up."
"3. Walk behind Mukuro, carrying it like a wedding dress train and nuzzling it tenderly."
Your choices, everyone!
"1. Let a pro do her hair."
"2. Have Shido tie it up."
"3. Walk behind Mukuro, carrying it like a wedding dress train and nuzzling it tenderly."
"Walk behind Mukuro,
carrying it like a wedding dress train
and nuzzling it tenderly..."
Who picked that?
Me! I did!
MARIA, you come up
with the choices, right?
Technically, I don't come up with them.
They're generated based on happiness level
and the date's progression.
I've always wondered: Is there always
a risky choice on purpose?
Yes. There's typically a favorite,
a contender, and a dark horse.
"A dark horse..."
Nobody's using MARIA's computing power
to predict horse racing, right?
Do "two." Just tie it up for her.
Wanna come to my house?
We've got combs and hair clips.
Mm. That sounds fun.
My hair is in your hands.
Ma'am, it's an honor.
You're good at this, Mister.
Well, Kotori always makes me
help with her hair.
Who is Kotori?
The girl with me yesterday.
She's my sister.
We should change your clothes.
You can borrow hers.
Mister, this won't work.
It's way too small.
No, not like that. Can't you
reproduce it with Spirit power?
Oh, that's what you meant!
Mm. That's more like it.
Eh? Why didn't you start with that?
Why'd you have her wear it, huh?
Well, shall we go, Mukuro?
Yeah, let's.
You were right--
today was a fun day.
You're really fond of that.
To think you'd do so much for me...
Could it be that you love Muku?
Yeah. I do, and I wanna protect you.
And I'm fond of you, too!
I love you, Shido.
But... don't you know?
By vowing yourself to Muku,
you vow to stay away
from those other girls.
Huh?
U-Uh, I can't make a promise like that
'cuz I wanna save all the Spirits.
Hmm?
I love the other Spirits I've sealed
as much as I love you.
So, I hope you can
get along with them, too.
You're too kind.
Okay, leave it to Muku.
Huh? What?
Well then, farewell for tonight.
Let's meet again soon, Mister.
Mukuro!
What's she thinking?
Morning, Kotori.
Good mor... ning...
Wh-What?!
Who are you?!
Why are you in my house?!
Huh? Uh, what are you
talking about, Kot--?
Get lost or I'll call the police!
Get outta here!
Who was that?!
The things people do sleepwalking...
Oh well. Guess I'll head to school.
Morning.
Hmm? Why the weird face, Tonomachi?
Uh... Sorry, who are you again?
A transfer student?
--Huh?
--Oh!
You must've been at karaoke!
Sorry! There were so many people,
I can't remember everyone.
What are you talking about, Tonomachi?
It's me, Shido Itsuka!
Shido... Itsuka? You guys know him?
Yamabuki, Hazakura, Fujibakama!
--Huh?!
D-Don't you guys know me?
Uh... What?
Ugh, is he hitting on us? So basic.
That's so lame.
They don't... know me?
Ah! Good morning, guys!
Tohka! Origami!
Huh? What's the matter?
The class is acting weird!
Was Kotori not sleepwalking?
Hmm? I'm not following you.
Who are you anyway?
C'mon, don't say that!
Lemme see your homework!
Negative. Do it yourself.
Gimme a break!
Kaguya! Yuzuru!
Mm?
You know me, right?!
Huh? Should I?
Baffled. Which class are you from?
Yeah, I'm coming. Delivery guy?
Huh? What? Are you a fan of mine?
Hello, Miku?
Random guys are calling me now!
Brr! Let's get shopping over with.
Yeah, let's go.
Yoshino! Natsumi! And Yoshinon!
Wh-What is it?
Whoa! Yikes...
Hey! You guys know me, right?
U-Um... Sorry, what's your name again?
I-I'm clueless.
Sorry, pal.
Dammit! What the hell's going on?!
Doesn't anyone know me?
Who's left? Reine, Kurumi,
the Ratatoskr crew, and...
Mukuro...! If I'm right about this...
Haniel!
Kaleidoscope!
If this is Mukuro's doing,
I can turn everything back to normal!
Segva.
Mukuro!
I thought you might
figure it out. Well done.
Did you make everyone forget me?
Yup! I locked their memories with Michael.
Neat, right? This way,
we can be all alone!
You can cherish Muku with all your heart.
Say, Mister...
You love Muku, don't you?
Yesterday, I met a strange guy at school.
He knew me and Origami.
Speaking of which,
I met a weirdo, too.
When I woke up, there was
a stranger in the kitchen.
Me, too. Some guy I don't know
was calling me yesterday.
"Call History"
"Darling"
"Darling" "Darling"
I immediately hung up,
but he's in my call history! See?!
"Darling"
Huh? "Darling"?!
I don't remember saving it! It's freaky!
Hey, Yuzuru. Could it be that guy?
Recollect. We met him, too.
Now that you mention it,
I chased away a weird fan at my place.
Us, too.
Yeah. He looked really
worried about something.
What's up, Origami?
My head started hurting.
You okay? Need to go home?
Origami! Hold on,
I'll call Ratatoskr's medical team.
No, it's all right.
I'm sorry to worry you.
Huh? O-Origami?
Yes? What is it?
Um, you're Origami, right?
I am, but I'm a different me than usual,
so it may surprise you.
More importantly,
is what you're saying true?
Nobody remembers him?
"Him"?
Who? Do you know, Yuzuru?
Negative. I have no idea.
I see. This must be Mukuro's doing.
In which case, what to do...?
H-Hold up. You're not making sense.
Who's Mukuro? And who's "Him"?
You guys should know. After all,
it was he, Shido Itsuka, who saved us.
Huh? Shido Itsuka?
The same last name as me?
Sh-Shido...
Tohka!
What's wrong? Now you, too?!
So much fun! Are you having fun?
Yeah. I am, Mukuro.
Good! Good! Do you love Muku?
Of course, I love you.
Muku, too! This is bliss!
Loving and being loved by someone
is such a wonderful thing!
Hey, Mukuro.
Hmm? What is it, Mister?
You said we were "close."
What did you mean by that?
That's just how it feels.
But if I had to say...
After you held Muku and we fell,
I saw a strange dream.
"Dream"?
A dream about a lonely,
young girl finding a family.
When Muku woke up,
Muku wanted to see you for some reason.
That dream is--
Itsuka!
I finally found you!
Huh? Origami?
Long time no see, Itsuka.
Are you this world's Origami?!
After Kurumi and I changed history?!
Yup! Though it's weird saying,
"Long time no see"
considering the other me
has been with you.
Origami! You remember who I am?!
Of course! But the other me doesn't
since her memories were locked.
I'm confused, but oh well.
I'll just lock your memories again.
Michael.
Mukuro, don't!
No! If you manifest your Angel,
they'll find you!
"Find you"? Who will?
There you are.
Tohka!
There's some extras here, too.
Hmph. No matter.
I'll turn you all into ashes.
Tohka! You're inverted?!
--Nehemoth!
--Begone.
Lataib.
How dare you defy my attack.
What's the matter with you?
That's my line. Your memories
should be locked by Michael.
If you intend to get in Muku's way,
I won't hold back!
Hold on!
--What?
--You dare to interfere?
U-Um... Please calm down and listen,
Mukuro... Tohka...
--Hmm?
--Tohka? Referring to me?
Yes! Mukuro loves Itsuka,
which is why she's upset
that you came for him.
Well, that's the gist of it.
But the thing is,
Itsuka hates violence.
Surely, there's a better way
to win Itsuka's love.
A-And Tohka...
What is your goal?
It's not to fight Mukuro, right?
As if goals matter.
I will not rest until I purge
the shame caused by this man.
As in, when you manifested
at DEM's base, right?
Well, even if you beat Itsuka using force,
can you truly say you beat him?
Use not force, but heart.
Unless you conquer his heart,
can it be true victory?
H-Hey, Origami?
What must I do to win his love?
What must I do to humiliate this man?
There is a way to do both
and determine a victor:
Go on a date, and the one
who steals Itsuka's lips wins!
Eh?!
Welcome home, Master!
Why are we doing this?
'Cuz it's best to be friends
before you kiss someone.
Not that! Why has Tohka inverted?
And why--? Whoa!
What are you whispering about?
Eat my damn strawberry already!
Itsuka!
What's your problem?
Ladies! Let's not cause a scene!
There are other masters here, so behave!
--Who the hell are you?
--What a weird outfit.
If you're too rowdy,
you'll trouble Master!
Hmm. What should we do?
I'll teach you magic words
to make Master hungry for cake!
Be tasty! Moe Moe Kyun!
There! Now Master can't wait
to eat cake! Right, Master?!
Huh? What?
He... can't... wait... to... eat... cake.
R-Right! Shido loves cakes!
Good! Now then, enjoy!
I see... I learned something new.
Be tasty! Moe Moe Kyun!
Now, feast like a dog!
What a vulgar woman.
Kissing is reserved for
establishing a relationship!
What... doing? Stay out... way!
"Episode 07:
'Locked Memories.'"
Mukuro! Tohka!
A world crisis. Humanity is in danger.
Can Shido save the world and Mukuro
against this planetary threat?
Next time: "Key and Sword."
"Episode 08: 'Key and Sword.'"
The Mukuro arc concludes!